appsamurai.com 2013-05-30

# Privacy Policy

**What information do we collect?**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

AppMyWorld uses Google FeedBurner to send a daily digest of new content from our website. If an individual want to use this service, they have to submit a valid email address to FeedBurner. Individuals who don’t want to share this personal information can still access our new content by visiting our [blog](http://www.appmyworld.com/blog/latest.html "AppMyWorld Blog"). Feedburner's privacy policy's cover the use of Feedburner. For more information, check out the [Feedburner](http://www.feedburner.com/fb/a/privacy "Feedburner Privacy Policy") and [Google](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ "Google Privacy Policy") privacy policies.

We use Google Analytics to measure the traffic on our site and app and this comes in the form of aggregate data. More info is provided by Google on their privacy policy here [Google Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ "Google Privacy Policy").

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

 **What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

-To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

-To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

-To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

-To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

-To send periodic emails.  The email address you provide will only be used to send you e-mail notifications about our products and services and special offers.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

 **Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent except as specified above.

 **Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not knowingly collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Violation of Privacy Policy**

AppMyWorld reserves the right to seek all remedies available at law and in equity for violations of the Privacy Policy as set forth in the website, including the right to block access from a particular Internet address to the website and to seek injunction relief.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

 **Terms Of Service  
**  
Please also visit our Terms Of Service section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website [here](http://www.appmyworld.com/terms-of-service.html).[  
](http://appmyworld.com/terms-of-service.html "Terms Of Service") **  
Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/) and terms of service.

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

If you have any questions, contact us [here](http://www.appmyworld.com/feedback.html).
